admeta.se 2010-06-21

# Privacy Policy

## GENERAL AGREEMENTS

##### Whitebox Echo

[ Whitebox Echo Direct Sales EULA (End-User Agreement for Advertisers)](http://www.admeta.se/images/stories/files/eula_%20echo_directsales_090228_appr.pdf "Whitebox Echo Direct Sales EULA \(End-User Agreement for Advertisers\)")

##### Whitebox Tango

[ Whitebox Tango Direct Sales EULA (End-User Agreement for Publishers and Sales Companies)](http://www.admeta.se/images/stories/files/eula%20tango%20direct%20sales%20090315_approved.pdf "Whitebox Tango Direct Sales EULA \(End-User Agreement for Publishers and Sales Companies\)")

## PRIVACY POLICY

This is a privacy policy for Admeta AB. Our homepage on the Web is located at http://www.admeta.com . The full text of our privacy policy is available on the Web at [http://www.admeta.com/w3c/privacypolicy.html](http://www.admeta.se/w3c/privacypolicy.html "Privacy Policy") . Users may go to <http://www.admeta.com/optinout/optinout.asp> for information on how to opt-in or opt-out of use of their information.

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address:

Admeta AB, HQ  
Vallgatan 26  
S-411 16 GÖTEBORG  
Phone +46 (0)31 23 34 50  
Telefax +46 (0)31 701 84 50

You may contact us by e-mail at [leif@admeta.com](mailto:leif@admeta.com) . You may call us at +46 31 23 33 50.

Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals  
We have the following privacy seals and/or dispute resolution mechanisms. If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, they can help you resolve your concern.

New Dispute: If you have any dispute regarding this P3P, please contact Leif at [leif@admeta.com](mailto:leif@admeta.com) .

Additional Information  
This policy is valid for 1 day from the time that it is loaded by a client.

## DATA COLLECTION

P3P policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as "statements"). This policy contains 2 data groups. The data practices of each group will be explained seperately.

Group "Basic information"

We collect the following information:

Click-stream data

HTTP protocol elements

Search terms

This data will be used for the following purposes:

· Completion and support of the current activity

· Web site and system administration

· Research and development

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:  
\- Data collected from all Web users: access logs, and search strings (if entered)

Group "Cookies"

At the user's option, we will collect the following data:

HTTP cookies

This data will be used for the following purposes:

· Research and development

· One-time tailoring

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:  
\- Cookies are used to track visitors to our site, so we can better understand what portions of our site best serve you.

## COOKIES

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

Our site makes use of cookies. Cookies are used for the following purposes:

· User targeting

· Research and development

## COMPACT POLICY SUMMARY

The compact policy which corresponds to this policy is:

CP="NOI DSP COR CURa ADMa DEVa TAIa OUR BUS IND UNI COM NAV INT"

The following table explains the meaning of each field in the compact policy:

Field  
Meaning

CP=  
This is the compact policy header; it indicates that what follows is a P3P compact policy.

NOI  
No identifiable information is collected, so no access is possible.

DSP  
The policy contains at least one dispute-resolution mechanism.

COR  
Violations of this policy will be corrected.

CURa  
The data is used for completion of the current activity.

ADMa  
The data is used for site administration.

DEVa  
The data is used for research and development.

TAIa  
The data is used for tailoring the site.

OUR  
The data is given to ourselves and our agents.

BUS  
Our business practices specify how long the data will be kept.

IND  
The data will be kept indefinitely.

UNI  
Unique identifiers are collected.

COM  
Computer information is collected.

NAV  
Navigation and clickstream data is collected.

INT  
Interactive data is collected.

The compact policy is sent by the Web server along with the cookies it describes. For more information, see the P3P deployment guide at <http://www.w3.org/TR/p3pdeployment> .

## POLICY EVALUATION

Microsoft Internet Explorer 6 will evaluate this policy's compact policy whenever it is used with a cookie. The actions IE will take depend on what privacy level the user has selected in their browser (Low, Medium, Medium High, or High; the default is Medium. In addition, IE will examine whether the cookie's policy is considered satisfactory or unsatisfactory, whether the cookie is a session cookie or a persistent cookie, and whether the cookie is used in a first-party or third-party context. This section will attempt to evaluate this policy's compact policy against Microsoft's stated behavior for IE6.

Note: this evaluation is currently experimental and should not be considered a substitute for testing with a real Web browser.

Satisfactory policy: this compact policy is considered satisfactory according to the rules defined by Internet Explorer 6. IE6 will accept cookies accompanied by this policy under the High, Medium High, Medium, Low, and Accept All Cookies settings.

Ethical Compliance Report by KPMG

Ethical Compliance Report by KPMG (PDF File)
